<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>My book blog</title><link>https://mybookblog.amelia-fromm.de/</link><description>Recent content on My book blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 11:00:07 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mybookblog.amelia-fromm.de/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hello, Universe</title><link>https://mybookblog.amelia-fromm.de/HelloUniverse/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 11:00:07 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://mybookblog.amelia-fromm.de/HelloUniverse/</guid><description>Buch: Hello Universe # In the book &amp;lsquo;Hello, Universe&amp;rsquo;, there are four persons with four perspectives. Kaori Tanaka, a would-be fortune teller, helps Virgil in some bad situations. Virgilio Salinas, also named Virgil, is a shy boy, hoping that someday Valencia will speak to him. Valencia Somerset, a girl with courage and assertiveness, is a person who is very intrested in nature. She studies squirrels, has a stray dog and knows the forest like her handback.</description></item><item><title>Die unlangweiligste Schule der Welt, Zeugnisalarm</title><link>https://mybookblog.amelia-fromm.de/unlangweiligste_schule/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 10:00:07 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://mybookblog.amelia-fromm.de/unlangweiligste_schule/</guid><description>Buch: Die unlangweiligste Schule der Welt: Zeugnisalarm! # Im Buch (das ist jetzt das Buch mit dem längstem Titel, worüber ich bis jetzt geschrieben habe) &amp;ldquo;Die (un)langweiligste Schule der Welt: Zeugnisalarm!&amp;rdquo; geht es darum, dass Maximilian &amp;ldquo;Maxe&amp;rdquo; Zack und Frieda Gehratewohl, gute Agenten der BfLb, der &amp;ldquo;Behörde für Langeweilebekämpfung&amp;rdquo; einen weiteren Auftrag bekommen.
Der Schulleiter kündigt nämlich an, das es auf den Zeugnissen sechsen für alle geben soll. Der Auftrag ist, dass die Kinder ihre eigentlichen Zeugnisse (mit den richtigen Noten) bekommen sollen.</description></item><item><title>Wonder</title><link>https://mybookblog.amelia-fromm.de/Wonder/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 18:00:07 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://mybookblog.amelia-fromm.de/Wonder/</guid><description>Book: Wonder # The Book &amp;lsquo;Wonder&amp;rsquo; is a book which is quite realistic. August &amp;lsquo;Auggie&amp;rsquo; Pullman, a ten-year-old kid, was born with a gene defect, which makes his face look &amp;lsquo;deformed&amp;rsquo;, as Julian describes it. Auggie was homeschooled until he was in 5th grade, and finally got to a real school.
Wonder is told from different perspectives, as for Summer&amp;rsquo;s (Auggies friend (NOT girlfriend)), Jack&amp;rsquo;s (Auggies friend) and Via&amp;rsquo;s (Auggies sister) perspective.</description></item><item><title>Book: Wizard of Once</title><link>https://mybookblog.amelia-fromm.de/wizard_once/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 19:00:07 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://mybookblog.amelia-fromm.de/wizard_once/</guid><description>This book is a book where you get to know a boy and a girl, both about the age of thirteen, the girl is a warrior, and the boy is a wizard.
It begins, I suppose, with the wizard boy. He is called Xar (pronouneced Zar, don&amp;rsquo;t ask me why, spelling is WEIRD), and he is the most disobedient boy of all wizards. The girl is called Wish, and has a very frantic with fear bodyguard.</description></item><item><title>Book: The wee free men</title><link>https://mybookblog.amelia-fromm.de/tiffany/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 11:00:07 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://mybookblog.amelia-fromm.de/tiffany/</guid><description>Book: The wee free men # The Wee Free Men are very little men who like &amp;ldquo;to fight, to drink and to drink and fight&amp;rdquo; (well, so they say&amp;hellip;!). Well, but the main character is Tiffany, at the beginning of the book she slais Jenny green-teeth with a friyng pan (for Jenny and all other fairies iron is very painful because iron is made by humans, not by nature - well, thats the short explanation), which seems to be very impressive to other witches.</description></item><item><title>Wrinkle in time</title><link>https://mybookblog.amelia-fromm.de/wrinkle_in_time/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 11:00:07 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://mybookblog.amelia-fromm.de/wrinkle_in_time/</guid><description>A Wrinkle in Time # A Wrinkle in time is a book that is very thrilling, especially for children. In the book there are three children and three witches, if you want to name women that can travel through time and space name witches&amp;hellip;
They travel to a planet that a big &amp;ldquo;IT&amp;rdquo; controls. They need to rescue the father from Meg, the main character in the book, the only problem is that this is anything but easy.</description></item><item><title>How to train your dragon - series</title><link>https://mybookblog.amelia-fromm.de/hiccup/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 11:00:07 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://mybookblog.amelia-fromm.de/hiccup/</guid><description>How to train your dragon # Hiccup is the hero of the story &amp;ldquo;How to train your dragon&amp;rdquo;. That is rather unbelievebale, because he is a very the normal Viking boy, with red hair and a dragon called Toothless, which, as the name says it, has no teeth.
His enemies at home are Snotface Snotlaut and Dogsbreath the Duhbrain. They are better than Hiccup in practically everything, exept maybe swordfighting.</description></item><item><title>Die Wilden Hühner</title><link>https://mybookblog.amelia-fromm.de/wilde_huehner/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 11:00:07 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://mybookblog.amelia-fromm.de/wilde_huehner/</guid><description>Die wilden Hühner sind eine Bande und Buchreihe, ich erzähle mal etwas über Hühner und Pygmäen
Die wilden Hühner wurden von Sprotte gegründet, sie ist aber keineswegs die Chefin der Mädchenbande. Da gibt es noch Melanie, auch die schöne Melanie genannt, Trude, die das Bandenhauptquartier besitzt, Frieda, Sprottes beste Freundin und Wilma, die erst später zugestiegen ist und immer eine mit Seifenwasser gefüllte Wasserpistole dabei hat. Es gibt auch die Pygmäen, die Feinde (manchmal Freunde) der Hühner.</description></item><item><title>Ruby - Band 3</title><link>https://mybookblog.amelia-fromm.de/Ruby/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 11:00:07 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://mybookblog.amelia-fromm.de/Ruby/</guid><description>Buch: Ruby - Band 3 # 1 Traumprinz, 100 peinliche Zettel und wie man sich ratzfatz wieder entliebt
Ruby ist eigentlich eine ganz normale Schülerin. Aber das kann man ja an jedem Anfang sagen.
Also von vorn. Ruby ist ein Mädchen, dessen Eltern sich geschieden haben. Ihre Mutter lebt in Grün-Berlin (keine Ahnung wo das ist) und ihr Vater in Bunt-Berlin (auch keine Ahnung wo das ist!). Sie hat ein paar Freundinen und alles ist OK, bis ein neur Mathelehrer kommt!</description></item><item><title>Echt Jetzt?!</title><link>https://mybookblog.amelia-fromm.de/EchtJetzt/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 11:00:07 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://mybookblog.amelia-fromm.de/EchtJetzt/</guid><description>Buch: Echt Jetzt?! # Das ist ein Buch für Kinder die es mit wirklich NERVIGEN Mamas zu tun haben. Genau so eine hat Lina nämlich.
Sie möchte einfach nur cool sein und an ihrer neuen Schule Freund*innen finden. (Also Lina, nicht die Mutter.) Sie hat aber manchmal Probleme, ziemlich große Probleme. Denn sie blamiert sich einfach ständig! Und dann ist sie auch noch umgezogen! Also wirklich:
Echt jetzt?!</description></item><item><title>Buch: Fox Girls</title><link>https://mybookblog.amelia-fromm.de/FoxGirls/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 11:00:07 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://mybookblog.amelia-fromm.de/FoxGirls/</guid><description>Buch: Fox Girls # Fox Girls ist ein deutsches Buch, keine Sorge. Es ist am Ende sehr spannend und cool. Die Geschichte fängt damit an, das zwei Mädchen einen Fuchs finden, ihn retten wollen und gebissen werden. Sie werden Gestaltenwandler und erleben ihr erstes Abenteuer. Ihr Freund, Kitsune, wird entführt und beinahe zu einem Sammler gebracht. Die &amp;ldquo;Jäger&amp;rdquo; sind Jäger, außer dass sie magische Lebewesen fangen und mit ihnen Handel treiben.</description></item><item><title>Book: Zusammenleben, was ist das?</title><link>https://mybookblog.amelia-fromm.de/zusammenleben/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 08:36:07 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://mybookblog.amelia-fromm.de/zusammenleben/</guid><description>Book: Zusammenleben, was ist das? # This is a book to read with children who have many curiosities. There are questions, answers and answers on the answers (yes, but&amp;hellip;).
This is a example;
Question: Must you respect the others all the time?
Answer:
No, because i can&amp;rsquo;t like all the people. Yes, but&amp;hellip;: Should you only respect the people who you like? Yes, but&amp;hellip;: Can you respect someone without liking him?</description></item><item><title>Book: Meine Freundin Roxy</title><link>https://mybookblog.amelia-fromm.de/meine_freundin_roxy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 10:55:07 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://mybookblog.amelia-fromm.de/meine_freundin_roxy/</guid><description>Book: Meine Freundin Roxy # Meine Freundin Roxy is a book for in tech interested children like me. Kenza Ait Si Abbou has written this cool book and Meike Topperwien has illustrated it. The book describes a little girl who finds a robot in a bush, takes it home. There together with her granny she repairs the robot and starts teaching it: She starts with simple language.
Girl: &amp;ldquo;This is a banana.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://mybookblog.amelia-fromm.de/about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2009 08:55:07 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://mybookblog.amelia-fromm.de/about/</guid><description>About this blog # This is Amelia&amp;rsquo;s book blog.</description></item></channel></rss>