<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Friendship on My book blog</title><link>https://mybookblog.amelia-fromm.de/tags/Friendship/</link><description>Recent content in Friendship on My book blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 11:00:07 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mybookblog.amelia-fromm.de/tags/Friendship/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hello, Universe</title><link>https://mybookblog.amelia-fromm.de/HelloUniverse/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 11:00:07 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://mybookblog.amelia-fromm.de/HelloUniverse/</guid><description>Buch: Hello Universe # In the book &amp;lsquo;Hello, Universe&amp;rsquo;, there are four persons with four perspectives. Kaori Tanaka, a would-be fortune teller, helps Virgil in some bad situations. Virgilio Salinas, also named Virgil, is a shy boy, hoping that someday Valencia will speak to him. Valencia Somerset, a girl with courage and assertiveness, is a person who is very intrested in nature. She studies squirrels, has a stray dog and knows the forest like her handback.</description></item><item><title>Wonder</title><link>https://mybookblog.amelia-fromm.de/Wonder/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 18:00:07 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://mybookblog.amelia-fromm.de/Wonder/</guid><description>Book: Wonder # The Book &amp;lsquo;Wonder&amp;rsquo; is a book which is quite realistic. August &amp;lsquo;Auggie&amp;rsquo; Pullman, a ten-year-old kid, was born with a gene defect, which makes his face look &amp;lsquo;deformed&amp;rsquo;, as Julian describes it. Auggie was homeschooled until he was in 5th grade, and finally got to a real school.
Wonder is told from different perspectives, as for Summer&amp;rsquo;s (Auggies friend (NOT girlfriend)), Jack&amp;rsquo;s (Auggies friend) and Via&amp;rsquo;s (Auggies sister) perspective.</description></item><item><title>Book: Wizard of Once</title><link>https://mybookblog.amelia-fromm.de/wizard_once/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 19:00:07 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://mybookblog.amelia-fromm.de/wizard_once/</guid><description>This book is a book where you get to know a boy and a girl, both about the age of thirteen, the girl is a warrior, and the boy is a wizard.
It begins, I suppose, with the wizard boy. He is called Xar (pronouneced Zar, don&amp;rsquo;t ask me why, spelling is WEIRD), and he is the most disobedient boy of all wizards. The girl is called Wish, and has a very frantic with fear bodyguard.</description></item><item><title>Wrinkle in time</title><link>https://mybookblog.amelia-fromm.de/wrinkle_in_time/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 11:00:07 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://mybookblog.amelia-fromm.de/wrinkle_in_time/</guid><description>A Wrinkle in Time # A Wrinkle in time is a book that is very thrilling, especially for children. In the book there are three children and three witches, if you want to name women that can travel through time and space name witches&amp;hellip;
They travel to a planet that a big &amp;ldquo;IT&amp;rdquo; controls. They need to rescue the father from Meg, the main character in the book, the only problem is that this is anything but easy.</description></item><item><title>How to train your dragon - series</title><link>https://mybookblog.amelia-fromm.de/hiccup/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 11:00:07 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://mybookblog.amelia-fromm.de/hiccup/</guid><description>How to train your dragon # Hiccup is the hero of the story &amp;ldquo;How to train your dragon&amp;rdquo;. That is rather unbelievebale, because he is a very the normal Viking boy, with red hair and a dragon called Toothless, which, as the name says it, has no teeth.
His enemies at home are Snotface Snotlaut and Dogsbreath the Duhbrain. They are better than Hiccup in practically everything, exept maybe swordfighting.</description></item></channel></rss>